<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

<!-- Common Words -->
	<string name="app_name">Craft Me A Pass</string>
	<string name="empty"></string>
    <string name="logo_description">L Logo</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>

<!-- Main Window -->
	<string name="who">Qui?</string>
    <string name="where">Où?</string>
    <string name="key">Clé</string>
    <string name="go_craft">Go Craft!</string>
    <string name="password_length">Longueur du Pass</string>
    <string name="password_type">Type de Pass</string>
    <string name="main_length_button">Longueur :</string>
    <string name="main_type_button">Type :</string>
    <string name="pass_settings">Configuration du Pass</string>
    <string name="common_length">Longueurs habituelles</string>
    <string-array name="common_sizes">
        <item >4</item>
        <item >6</item>
        <item >8</item>
        <item >10</item>
        <item >12</item>
        <item >16</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="crafting">Craft en cours&#8230;</string>
    
<!-- Result Window -->
	<string name="title_activity_result">Mot de passe fabriqué</string>
	<string name="pass_window_title">Votre mot de passe</string>
	<string name="pass_copy_button">Copier</string>
	<string name="pass_label">Votre mot de passe est :</string>
    
<!-- Menu -->
    <string name="settings">Préférences</string>
    <string name="howto">Guide</string>
    <string name="clear_clipboard">Vider le presse-papiers</string>
    <string name="quit">Quitter</string>
    
<!-- Settings -->
	<string name="punctuation">Ponctuation</string>
	<string name="punctuation_summary">ex : "#~!</string>
    <string name="space">Espace</string>
    <string name="space_summary"> </string>
	<string name="save">Sauvegarder</string>
    <string name="size">Taille</string>
    <string name="can_your_password_have">Votre pass peut-il contenir&#8230;</string>
    <string name="length">Longueur</string>
    <string name="pass_length">Longueur du pass</string>
    <string name="input_to_lowercase">Convertir les champs en minuscule</string>
    <string name="input_to_lowercase_title">Convertir les champs en minuscule</string>
    <string name="input_to_lowercase_summary">Si vous l\'eteignez, \"Ca\" et \"ca\" vous donneront deux mots de passe complètement différents.</string>
    <string name="numbers">Chiffres</string>
    <string name="uppercase_letters">Majuscules</string>
    <string name="lowercase_letters">Minuscules</string>
    <string name="conversion_settings">Preferences de Connexion</string>
    <string name="pass_template">Templates de Mots de passe</string>
    <string name="use_old_algorithm">Utiliser l\'ancien algorithme</string>
    <string name="use_old_algorithm_summary">Vieil algorithme bancal présent dans les versions Beta</string>
    <string-array name="pass_type">
        <item >Code PIN</item>
        <item >Alphanumerique</item>
        <item >Que des lettres</item>
        <item >Toutes options</item>
        <item >Autre</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="settings_list">
        <item >@string/lowercase_letters</item>
        <item >@string/uppercase_letters</item>
        <item >@string/numbers</item>
        <item >@string/punctuation</item>
        <item >@string/space</item>
        <item >@string/pass_length</item>
    </string-array>
    
    
    
    
    
    
<!-- How-to -->
	<string name="howto_title">Comment crafter?</string>
    <string name="close">Fermer</string>
    <string name="previous">Précédent</string>
    <string name="next">Suivant</string>
    <string name="copy_toast">Mot de passe copié dans le presse-papiers</string>
	<string name="howto_who"> &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212; Qui &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;</string>
    <string name="howto_where"> &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212; Où &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;</string>
    <string name="howto_key"> &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212; Clé &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;</string>
	<string-array name="howto_array">
    	<item >Bonjour et bienvenue dans cet app crafteuse de mots de passe.\n\n\t En quelques étapes, je vais vous montrer comment vous crafter un nouveau mot de passe que seul vous pouvez trouver, et que vous n\'aurez même pas à retenir !</item>
    	<item >1 - Dans la case "Qui", rentrez un nom qui désigne la personne qui utilisera ce mot de passe. Ca peut être "Nom", "Prénom Nom", "Surnom", etc..\nSouvenez-vous juste que vous devrez rentrer la même information la prochaine fois.</item>
    	<item >2 - Dans la case "Où", rentrez un nom qui désigne l\'endroit où vous vous inscrivez. Par exemple, pour facebook vous pouvez rentrer \"Facebook\", \"FB\", \"facebook.com\" etc&#8230; \nEncore une fois, il faudra s\'en souvenir&#8230;</item>
    	<item >3 - Dans la case "Clé", rentrez un mot, une combinaison de mots, ou quoi que ce soit qui vous est familier. Votre mot de passe sera crypté selon ce mot alors choisissez bien. Ca peut être vide, un caractère, un livre, à vous de voir.</item>
    	<item >4 - Ensuite, cliquez sur ce gros bouton vert. L\'app vous amène ensuite à votre nouveau mot de passe, généré à partir des informations que vous avez rentré.</item>
    	<item >La prochaine fois où vous aurez besoin de ce mot de passe, tout ce que vous avez à faire est de rentrer les mêmes informations, et l\'app vous rendra le même mot de passe.\nAussi, n\'hésitez pas à jouer avec les settings pour brouiller encore plus les pistes. Mais gardez-bien en tête : Chaque changement donne un pass différent&#8230;</item>
    </string-array>
	
	
	
	
	
	
	<string name="about_text">
	    Hi, and welcome to my app : Craft me a pass!
        \n\n\tNowadays, we all have multiple passwords that we have to remember for multiple sites. Many will choose easy passes (1234, password, etc&#8230;) and even keep the same pass, no matter the number of places where they registered.Moreover, sometimes they register for others (while setting up a WiFi router in your girlfriend\'s house etc&#8230;) and still use that same pass.
        \n\tThis app was made to counter that. It generates a pass that will be different for every site you want to register, without you having to remember all of them, needing another pass to access them, or stocking them anywhere but in your brain.
		\n\n\tHere is how it works :
		\n\n
		\n1-\t Put whatever suits the place you\'re registering on the best in the box called \"Where\" (ex : for Facebook : Facebook, facebook, fb, Facebook.com, etc&#8230;)
        \n2-\t Put whatever suite the person who\'s registering in the best in the box called \"Who\" (ex: your full name, your nickname, the way you want to be called, with caps, without, etc&#8230;)
        \n3-\t Choose a key, that is the thing that you\'ll have to remember. It can be hard, or easy, just remember that you have to keep this one in mind for the next time you want your pass.
        \n(3bis-\t Change the Settings to match the requirements for the place where you are registering)
        \n4-\t Press the \"Go Craft\" button. The app will give you a pass generated by the info you gave. You can also copy it so you dont have to type all the strange characters
        \n5-\t When you want to get the password again for the next time you log in, you enter the same infos in the app (or in the Web Version, or any other version for that matter) and it will give it back
        \n
        \nIMPORTANT : The application does not stock anything. That means even if your device gets hacked, nobody gets your passes or even the infos you input (except what is left in the Clipboard maybe but they won\'t know for which place you used it)
        \n\t That also means I have no way to give you back any password. Nothing is stocked. Just try the combinations that you can remember, and for the next time\&#8230; use a more simple pattern.
        \n
        \n(Hint : You have to choose a pattern, a way to put these infos. It can be simple (ex: Where = with a cap at the beginning, no space, no .com, .net, or any address \/ Who = Your full name with Caps at the beginning \/ Key = Your girlfriend\'s name), or tricky (A different key for the kind of site, different patterns if it is a site or something else, etc\&#8230;), but remember that this tool has been made to giving you a hard to find password without you having to remember all of it&#8230; Having to remember a bazillion patterns would most likely render the app uneffective)
		\n
        \nQuentin D. quentin\@devauchelle.eu
	</string>
	
	

</resources>
